that if home level recording and right now I turn on
method 20 of staff then it
is very big
that ah
no meaning meaning the voice recording will
not come to you I will record it and
send it to you sir okay whatever happens will
remain with me whatever will remain with me is my
stomach is there any such system when check returns
how are you people do if they
very good very good
a in private school okay very
good in which school are you busy twice okay okay
very good my brother
is also a teacher but he is a government employee this is in
KVS in chapter 4 Dwarka sector 12 Dwarka and porn okay good
I am currently 19 years old hellish and
person sir this is the plan for such a Monday
and in this a total of plus one is required will be covered together
you can see this chat box
grh grh write the details and share it for your knowledge you can
subscribe you can take photos in
it according to my date of birth
I have written a cup of cream in it according to your face
cream or before doing something like this
you are seeing  Now if the school
subscribes and cuts it, then
subscribe and if you subscribe for this decision
and soon everyone will
take the policy with basic, so that you can take
this plan with this and you
can also take 50 plans with your partner and you can take the same combination with 10 lakhs, with
which you can
top up 50 plans with 10 lakhs,
so if 50 plans become small or big, it will
increase more than your plan, then the plan is very
cheap for you and how will I check this, I have
used five Lucky Ali plans, you will get
15000 rupees for 364 rupees, if you piece this
and add it, then you will have to pay 20 loop real only for
9554 rupees, from 15000 and often
give, so the total plan is 25 lakhs,
you are seeing 5 lakhs rs. 15000 and you have to
take 20 lakhs for 9000 ₹500, so this is cheap minimum
idea, it will cost 5 lakhs 750 rupees  So there were
10552 notes in exchange of 500, so political or else
tell me that there is
some increase in Bhagwan Nagar, friend
I get sick, my child has been given this,
my increase is there and my second
Hussain Razi at that time ₹50 does not support, if I
fold it then I can do it, otherwise it cannot happen, if it cannot happen then it will not happen,
payment will have to be made
in that relationship and I had talked to this
madam, tell me you went to Pasha, first of all
I will get you Jeev Asan, you will be available
in all the options, I will tell you about everything also,
but first I do not understand you, this
Ghagra which you take 5 lakh or 10 lakh,
you will have to use it in the Panchayat on airplane mode
and Sahridya, without a credit card there
is no option for mi, the first thing and so
whatever you understand, 5 lakh or dal with 25,
if
you have used it due to any emergency then you can use it again,
okay, your bread may or may
not work at the age of 45 and I will tell you in the next  If you
quote for 1 year then your premium will increase
because you will be 46 years old. So
you have a choice. If you take a 2 year premium on this today
then it will be cheaper for you. I am
in this field. I am like this. I
will explain to you from the previous chapter, in
which your money will be saved. The 15000 rupees you have spent now, make it
22000 rupees after-
effects. Please friend, it will cost five to
seven thousand rupees next year. Yes, because of this position,
okay sir,
you are busy in some work. Now the
insurance increases on this side. Here,
money is never returned in health insurance.
If there are love couples, then 10 percent
bonus will increase on it. When we say no claim bonus, the
solution to your problem will become 5.5 lakhs.
And in Delhi, you will get your decision.
If your test lab is changing then only your
premium will increase. If you are going through the same lab, it will remain
free. There will be
no effect. You will get some discount on experience. The
insurance will keep increasing. Subscribe and
subscribe and
call in your wife's name.  I hope
you will already get the answer from today itself and will take it
for the completion,
okay, okay, if you want ghee, you can make it, you
can take it, it is not like that
whoever is elder in the family will give you readymade
questions, I will talk to you about liquid liner,
when I am chatting with you, I keep
thinking a little about the plan,
you should see this, hello master plan, you must be
seeing this, if you
take any health insurance plan, then it will be
mandatory to have a 24-hour hospitalization without
admission, no plan is successful
for you, you cannot take it
without 24-hour admission and if you take it for the first time, then the
first 30 days will be cigarette, for the first
30 days we will
not get any claim, but it has been started very successfully
and if there is any need due to acid, then
I will be informed about the intake, it has
all kinds of accident cover, so if there is a
fall from the stairs, or any
kind of thing, then mustard will be included in it,
okay, okay, when new episodes you and  Let's
talk about its other features, the
plan here is that anyone from 18 years to lifelong can
take it yearly, like electricity, it will be
covered for 20 years, now the
son is 19 years old, the part will be covered
and next year the insurance will be covered,
minimum 5 lakhs can be taken from the body and maximum up to 50 lakhs
and there is
no pre-medical test in this policy,
if you are withdrawing this plan for the first time, even if you are 65 years old, there is
no medical test, if you were
above 65 then you would have to undergo medical test first and then only you will
get the policy, everything
is fine when admitted and the expenses before that are
covered in this policy for 30 days,
which we call free
hospitalization, whenever a person is
sick, he is not directly admitted to the hospital,
first you come to the doctor for treatment,
10 minutes, 15 days, 20 days, finally 1431
normal, so that you need to get admitted, so the
expenses of Bhushan, in which doctor's
fees have been paid, medicines, tests have been done,
kidneys cover all those expenses  You will sleep on the collapsed channel,
if you are admitted for a day, if you are
not admitted, then we cannot take this money, how will
this hole be, how will it be,
that is our job, we will wait for you,
hence the role of the agent is played, okay,
this is all right,
suppose you are admitted in the hospital for two-four days, that is,
noodles, and the doctor
says that you are getting discharged today,
but the course is not complete yet, then
all those expenses will also be covered for seven days, even if
you are on medicines, then give that
bill also, we will reverse that money also, the
entire hospital expense will be cashless,
I am telling you this again, again the
previous expenses and after discharge, those
medicines which are not available in the hospital, the poor will have to take, if we take them along, then
when will that money be given in our body, and no, the ambulance
is covered, when any kind of ambulance is
needed, then hospitalization at ₹15,
you can use the ambulance in our body, the
room will be like this, there is
no limit, no matter how much a single private AC room costs,
you can get treatment in any big hospital  You can do this at home, whether it is
Apollo, your hospital, any
Aakash hospital, anywhere, already. If we
talk about the complete list of treatment plans, then there will be a
list of 1000 hospitals in Juice, all of them will be
shared with you on WhatsApp. If this
policy does not come clear in this year's policy,
you will get 10 percent no claim bonus
and it will increase up to 50%.
If you have a recovery of 5 lakhs, then it will
increase by 50,000 and at the maximum it will
increase up to Rs. 7.5 lakhs. Is this the same thing?
If there is any plan for emergency surgery, or if there is
any plan number in C service, there will be a
waiting period for its swab to be taken. For the first
2 years, you
cannot take treatment for these diseases like
cataract, hernia, fibroids, fibroids, fibroids
related issues, joint replacement, these are the
names of some diseases. You should
also write these on the fly, we will meet you, then you will laugh, then
their specifics will be written, today you do
not have any problem, but God forbid,
after 2 minutes, 6 months, students will
complain about these things.  If needed, there will be no
shortage for the first 2 years. We will talk about 163 here
and he gets hundred percent here
or what I explained to him,
5 minutes 75 lakhs free with 10 lakhs, 10
lakhs medium, that means whether your tea is completely
finished or not, if you get any decision from the
cabinet, when will the first step of four lakhs come and if your
glamour pass is put, then also the shortage will be passed
and there is a condition, we will display it from the same person,
like my family, husband, wife, one
child, my claim of four lakhs has come for cancer,
in the same year, now except me,
my wife is my child, if anyone puts
clamps, then we will pass it or for me
also cancer and leave it, if it
comes for me, then also we have passed our five fatal passes,
but if I get three lakh rupees for cancer in my throat, then
whatever balance is left,
I can use that as a new resource from
time to time, if anyone already has a
chronic disease, I also asked you, do
you take any medicine etc., this message,
BP shop, soon, then it is very good  Sir, this is
for those people who are
taking the policy after childhood, after 80, then
they have some or the other thing, if they also
delete it, then it will take 2 years of
meeting minutes from the front, if you are fit and fine healthy
then there is no meeting for you,
everyone has to wait for a cyclone after 30 days, okay, let's
talk about the next 9 news statement,
Ayushman in the policy means when there are any such
treatments which are 9 allopathic treatments,
Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha,
Homeopathy, all these treatments in our body,
you will be covered up to 100 percent,
you will not only have a plan of Rs 50 lakh, that is
why you can use it,
okay, it is very important that we have an
in-house TPA in our body and I always explain to people that
whichever company has an in-house TPA,
it means that every party administrator, the
company from which you have taken the policy, that
company settles your claim, then that
policy is very good, so in-house
speech and claim settlement help
is free in our body, only  After 5 minutes you get
your settlement guaranteed in our Andheri flat
and 45
minutes ago Delhi happens that there was
no sorrow from the serial, it pays that penalty
which no one in the entire industry gives
and interference does not matter but
giving guarantee in itself matters, all
that thing is covered in our two
Jitendra policies, animals are
covered in dog bite policy, when we talk about plus organ donor,
you can use Temples and Homes MS word and there are three types of neck,
when it will be bone marrow transplant, if
you have liver transplant or
kidney transplant,
you can still take it from family members only, you
cannot take it from that person, when
you are taking it from, the company will bear the
entire expense up to the time percentage of the time left,
okay, from his joining to whatever will be there
for him, everything will be
clicked and if someone deletes it, due to which
your luck is nothing, there is something which
Khusro has BP, if he
does, then the companies put loading on it,
they have to charge 5% (15 cents)
extra premium.
This point is not applicable on your body. If
someone has a medical test, which is primary,
he will declare it, then he will have to pay this money. It is
not applicable to you.
Next, we will talk about it. You will
get two help every year in the policy, when the health is
best. Home visit is a home visit. You
can get a health checkup done once a year for both.
These features are available in the policy only after 15 days of taking the policy. There is no
shortage of it, whether your claim comes or not,
you can use it every year. Its
cost is not wasted, which is very good.
When 1919 is a
widget,
anyone can earn money. Sir, there is
no need to go to the hospital. I have written it very clearly,
home visit, you can call the number at home,
you will not have to go first. And
nowadays there is a redmi situation due to Karuna, at this
time no one thinks it is
appropriate to go to the hospital, people
get a doctor at home, this machine and your
blood  We take the pair of slippers from home
and your report reaches you in two days on your mail.
Our player settlement is very helpful and
free of cost. We use Artificial Intelligence. There is no
such shortage in the entire industry
which does
PM settlement through Artificial Intelligence. It means that
your claim is processed within minutes. In
some cases, it is fever,
dengue and chikungunya, loose motion or
dehydration. This small screenshot shows that the cost
of the van is Rs. 2025/- to Rs. 50,000. If a
patient is admitted for these things
and the claim of our company's
customer goes to the hospital, then the hospital
gives approval there in not less than * minutes, in which our
manpower is involved. Our
Artificial Intelligence system has been
created in the system,
nobody asks for these small things.
Our customer will
not get admitted to the hospital happily, in case of emergency or
in trouble, or for these things, he will
get some other approval. This is the
biggest problem in the entire industry.  It
is fast, this thing is available with us and the
big news here is the cheapest premium cost
in the whole world. If you
look at a time injury of Rs 50 lakh, then
our decision is supported by half the pricing of other companies,
which if you do
not have these features and in this policy, on
taking formation in summer for 2 years, you get 10 percent on
this account and you in racket age,
as I told you, you are a black
year here, whereas next year you will be 40 years old, which
today is 15000 problem, Avni Aman will be of 21 thousand
rupees, so this is the quantity, 15000
* two pieces 1000 - teenagers will get these hair
products, 27200 will be available from Birbal,
now you will take crotch for 15000
and visor will give 15 and 2237 claims will have to be given next year, if
we collect over 10,000 points counter, then it will be good for you,
everything is my personal session, that
his fate is total presentation, which we
side, everyone goes, hope  I will tell you
that you must have understood, if there is something
that you do not want then now we
can discuss 221, along with this, if you have
decided anything on your own, please
note down the Aadhar number of the strong gods from here, I am putting it in the chat box, it is
my number
and the one which I have told my mother,
you should also take a photo of it in your mobile, then
you will have the same easy services
and I hope your details are ok.